<resources>

    <string name="app_name">SEJcomp</string>
    <string name="sc1">You are walking through an enchanted forest with gigantic trees as tall as mountains and as thick as large lakes.
You got here magically teleported into a distant planet in a distant galaxy in the future.
You see one such tree with a cave-like structure at its base. What do you do?</string>
    <string name="sc1_op1">Enter the cave</string>
    <string name="sc1_op2">You look around, and realise there is another road slightly skewed to the cave entrance.</string>
    <string name="sc2_1">You enter  the dark hollow of an ancient tree that has had earthlings like you in the past.
This tree is called the tree of the undying, where death won\'t touch you.
On the other hand, pain can - if you don\'t make the right moves. And then you have to live with the pain for eternity.
You are suddenly sucked into a vortex, finding yourself at a crossroads of sorts.
From here, you can go north-east or north-west</string>
    <string name="sc2_2">You have been walking for miles... and this is getting frustrating. Will this road ever end?
Suddenly, a dagger falls from the skies above. What do you do?</string>
    <string name="sc2_1op1">North-East</string>
    <string name="sc2_1op2">North-West</string>
    <string name="sc2_2op1">Pick up the dagger</string>
    <string name="sc2_2op2">Decide not to pick it up</string>
    <string name="sc3_1">You walk for miles into what seems like an endless abyss. And then he presents himself. The evil Cthulhu.
He, it, or whatever - stares at you and you go insane.
Do you flee for your life or eat your head?</string>
    <string name="sc3_2">lo and behold! A handsome prince stands before you.
Suddenly, his iris turns into a deep red color. You are frightened.
Yet, you find yourself helplessly attracted to the prince. Now, you have a choice to make.
Do you kill him or kiss him?</string>
    <string name="sc3_1op1">Flee for your life</string>
    <string name="sc3_1op2">Approach the strange creature, trembling</string>
    <string name="sc3_2op1">Kiss the handsome princess</string>
    <string name="sc3_2op2">Stab him in the heart with the dagger</string>
    <string name="sc4_1">You have been betrayed by your lecherous lust. This god of desire turns into a dragon and burns you to dust.
Wrong move friend. You shall be lost forever into the infinite abyss of the tree of the undead.</string>
    <string name="sc4_2">What a murderous and sinful thing you just committed. However, the dead body suddenly, vaporises, and you realise that you just killed
one of the most evil demons to have walked the face of this world.</string>
    <string name="sc4_1op1">You\'re dead. End game.</string>
    <string name="sc4_1op2">You\'re dead. End game.</string>
    <string name="sc4_2op1">You\'re alive. Congrats, you just won the game.</string>
    <string name="sc4_2op2">You\'re alive. Congrats, you just won the game.</string>
    <string name="sc5_1">You didn\'t pick up the dagger. You continue walking, and see this demon-like figure suddenly appear out of nowhere.
You panic, and realise that you have no weapon to defend yourself with. Suddenly, it senses your vulnerability, and teleports the both of y\'all
into a room, with your back against the wall. It approaches you, step by step, and engulfs you in a dark smoke like vapour, and you cease to exist.</string>
    <string name="sc5_1op1">You\'re dead. End game.</string>
    <string name="sc5_1op2">You\'re dead. End game.</string>
    <string name="honor_value">Honor</string>
    <string name="player_name">Nathan Drake</string>

</resources>
